exam_quest = [
  {
    showResults: 1,
    skipExam: 0,
    randQ: 0,
    countQ: 5,

    //1
    question: "Why is it important to recognize the types of data considered sensitive or confidential within your work context?",
    answer: 2, //1-first, 2-second, 4-third, 8-fourth
    answers: [
      "To increase device performance.",
      "To prevent unauthorized access and protect sensitive information.",
      "To access restricted websites.",
      "To improve battery life.",
    ],
  },
  {
    //2
    question: "What is one personal responsibility in protecting work-related data on personal devices?",
    answer: 4, 
    answers: [
      "Sharing work-related data with family and friends.",
      "Ignoring security warnings and notifications.",
      "Using strong, unique passwords for accounts.",
      "Storing work-related data on unsecured cloud storage.",
    ],
  },

  {
    //3
    question: "What is a recommended practice for creating passwords for different accounts and services?",
    answer: 4, 
    answers: [
      "Using the same password for all accounts.",
      "Using weak and easily guessable passwords.",
      "Using strong, unique and unleaked passwords for each account.",
      "Sharing passwords with colleagues.",
    ],
  },

  {
    //4
    question: "Why is it important to regularly update software on personal devices?",
    answer: 2, 
    answers: [
      "To decrease device security.",
      "To enhance device performance and to maintain the latest security patch level.",
      "To prevent software updates.",
      "To improve battery life.",
    ],
  },

  {
    //5
    question: "What is one purpose of using reputable security software on personal devices?",
    answer: 2, 
    answers: [
      "To slow down device performance.",
      "To prevent, detect and remove threats such as viruses and malware.",
      "To increase internet speed.",
      "To access restricted websites.",
    ],
  },
];

fin_game = [
  {
    // 1 = true, 2 = false
    question:
      "Regularly updating your device's operating system and applications is optional for protecting against known threats.",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    // 1 = true, 2 = false
    question:
      "It is safe to use public or unsecured Wi-Fi networks for work-related communication to save data costs.",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    // 1 = true, 2 = false
    question:
      "Recognizing signs of threats includes being vigilant for unusual activity on your device, such as unexpected pop-ups or slow performance.",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    // 1 = true, 2 = false
    question:
      "Installing a reliable antivirus program on your device is unnecessary to maintain security.",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    // 1 = true, 2 = false
    question:
      "Mixing personal and work-related data on one device poses a significant risk because it facilitates data breaches and unauthorized access.",
    answer: 1,
  },
];
